(Olivia Hye's LOOΠΔ TV has been started!)
#NowPlaying "LOOΠΔ / Olviia Hye - Egoist (Feat. JinSoul)"
Yves: Hello!
Go Won: Hello!
Chuu: Lo!
Go Won: Lo!
Yves: We're LOOΠΔ Long Legs Unit~
(Here comes Olivia Hye!)
Olivia Hye: Helloooo~
(She was alreday revealed on LOOΠΔ TV for Up&amp;Line)
Olivia Hye: I was really waiting for that video.
Olivia Hye: So I watched as soon as it's released!
Olivia Hye: But my face wasn't showing up.
Olivia Hye: So I'm nervous but also wonder what the peoples' reaction would be!
Olivia Hye: When will it be opened?
Chuu: When will it be opened?
(She'll be tied up all day!)
Go Won: Busy~
(Transformation!)
Olivia Hye: Hello
Olivia Hye: I'm Olivia Hye, the twelfth membef of LOOΠΔ!
Olivia Hye: Even it will be blurred?
Olivia Hye: I was very awkward
Olivia Hye: When I filmed LOOΠΔ TV last time.
Olivia Hye: Of course, I'm still awkward...
Olivia Hye: I'm trying my best not to show it
(Please looking forward to Olivia Hye's LOOΠΔ TV!)